<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Everyday cve</title>
  
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/"/>
  <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.821Z</updated>
  <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>John Doe</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.31</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-31/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-31/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.824Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.821Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-7198" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-7198</a><br>OMERO before 5.0.6 has multiple CSRF vulnerabilities because the framework for OMERO’s web interface lacks CSRF protection.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10664" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10664</a><br>Domoticz before 4.10578 allows SQL Injection via the idx parameter in CWebServer::GetFloorplanImage in WebServer.cpp.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10672" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10672</a><br>treeRead in hdf/btree.c in libmysofa before 0.7 does not properly validate multiplications and additions.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10678" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10678</a><br>Domoticz before 4.10579 neglects to categorize \n and \r as insecure argument options.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-7198&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2014-7198&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMERO before 5
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.30</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-30/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-30/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.822Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.817Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10647" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10647</a><br>ZZZCMS zzzphp v1.6.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code via a .php URL in the plugins/ueditor/php/controller.php?action=catchimage source[] parameter because of a lack of inc/zzz_file.php restrictions. For example, source%5B%5D=http%3A%2F%2F192.168.0.1%2Ftest.php can be used if the 192.168.0.1 web server sends the contents of a .php file (i.e., it does not interpret a .php file).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10648" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10648</a><br>Robocode through 1.9.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause external service interaction (DNS), as demonstrated by a query for a unique subdomain name within an attacker-controlled DNS zone, because of a .openStream call within java.net.URL.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10649" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10649</a><br>In ImageMagick 7.0.8-36 Q16, there is a memory leak in the function SVGKeyValuePairs of coders/svg.c, which allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted image file.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10650" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10650</a><br>In ImageMagick 7.0.8-36 Q16, there is a heap-based buffer over-read in the function WriteTIFFImage of coders/tiff.c, which allows an attacker to cause a denial of service or information disclosure via a crafted image file.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10652" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10652</a><br>An issue was discovered in flatCore 1.4.7. acp/acp.php allows remote authenticated administrators to upload arbitrary .php files, related to the addons feature.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10654" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10654</a><br>The lzo1x_decompress function in liblzo2.so.2 in LZO 2.10, as used in Long Range Zip (aka lrzip) 0.631, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (invalid memory read and application crash) via a crafted archive, a different vulnerability than CVE-2017-8845.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10655" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10655</a><br>Grandstream GAC2500 1.0.3.35, GXP2200 1.0.3.27, GVC3202 1.0.3.51, GXV3275 before 1.0.3.219 Beta, and GXV3240 before 1.0.3.219 Beta devices allow unauthenticated remote code execution via shell metacharacters in a /manager?action=getlogcat priority field, in conjunction with a buffer overflow (via the phonecookie cookie) to overwrite a data structure and consequently bypass authentication. This can be exploited remotely or via CSRF because the cookie can be placed in an Accept HTTP header in an XMLHttpRequest call to lighttpd.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10656" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10656</a><br>Grandstream GWN7000 before 1.0.6.32 devices allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code via shell metacharacters in the filename in a /ubus/uci.apply update_nds_webroot_from_tmp API call.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10657" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10657</a><br>Grandstream GWN7000 before 1.0.6.32 and GWN7610 before 1.0.8.18 devices allow remote authenticated users to discover passwords via a /ubus/uci.apply config request.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10658" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10658</a><br>Grandstream GWN7610 before 1.0.8.18 devices allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code via shell metacharacters in the filename in a /ubus/controller.icc.update_nds_webroot_from_tmp update_nds_webroot_from_tmp API call.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10659" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10659</a><br>Grandstream GXV3370 before 1.0.1.41 and WP820 before 1.0.3.6 devices allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code via shell metacharacters in a /manager?action=getlogcat priority field.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10660" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10660</a><br>Grandstream GXV3611IR_HD before 1.0.3.23 devices allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code via shell metacharacters in the /goform/systemlog?cmd=set logserver field.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10661" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10661</a><br>On Grandstream GXV3611IR_HD before 1.0.3.23 devices, the root account lacks a password.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10662" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10662</a><br>Grandstream UCM6204 before 1.0.19.20 devices allow remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary code via shell metacharacters in the backupUCMConfig file-backup parameter to the /cgi? URI.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10663" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10663</a><br>Grandstream UCM6204 before 1.0.19.20 devices allow remote authenticated users to conduct SQL injection attacks via the sord parameter in a listCodeblueGroup API call to the /cgi? URI.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10647&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-10647&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;ZZZCMS zzzph
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.29</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-29/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-29/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.820Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.817Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9605" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9605</a><br>PHP Scripts Mall Online Lottery PHP Readymade Script 1.7.0 has Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the err value in a .ico picture upload.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9695" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9695</a><br>Norton Core prior to v278 may be susceptible to an arbitrary code execution issue, which is a type of vulnerability that has the potential of allowing an individual to execute arbitrary commands or code on a target machine or in a target process. Note that this exploit is only possible with direct physical access to the device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9918" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9918</a><br>An issue was discovered in the Harmis JE Messenger component 1.2.2 for Joomla!. Input does not get validated and queries are not written in a way to prevent SQL injection. Therefore arbitrary SQL-Statements can be executed in the database.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9919" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9919</a><br>An issue was discovered in the Harmis JE Messenger component 1.2.2 for Joomla!. It is possible to craft messages in a way that JavaScript gets executed on the side of the receiving user when the message is opened, aka XSS.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9920" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9920</a><br>An issue was discovered in the Harmis JE Messenger component 1.2.2 for Joomla!. It is possible to perform an action within the context of the account of another user.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9921" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9921</a><br>An issue was discovered in the Harmis JE Messenger component 1.2.2 for Joomla!. It is possible to read information that should only be accessible by a different user.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9922" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9922</a><br>An issue was discovered in the Harmis JE Messenger component 1.2.2 for Joomla!. Directory Traversal allows read access to arbitrary files.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9604" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9604</a><br>PHP Scripts Mall Online Lottery PHP Readymade Script 1.7.0 has Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) for Edit Profile actions.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6481" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6481</a><br>Abine Blur 7.8.2431 allows remote attackers to conduct “Second-Factor Auth Bypass” attacks by using the “Perform a right-click operation to access a forgotten dev menu to insert user passwords that otherwise would require the user to accept a second-factor request in a mobile app.” approach, related to a “Multifactor Auth Bypass, Full Disk Encryption Bypass” issue affecting the Affected Chrome Plugin component.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-20378" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-20378</a><br>The L2CAP signaling channel implementation and SDP server implementation in OpenSynergy Blue SDK 3.2 through 6.0 allow remote, unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a denial of service via malicious L2CAP configuration requests, in conjunction with crafted SDP communication over maliciously configured L2CAP channels. The attacker must have connectivity over the Bluetooth physical layer, and must be able to send raw L2CAP frames. This is related to L2Cap_HandleConfigReq in core/stack/l2cap/l2cap_sm.c and SdpServHandleServiceSearchAttribReq in core/stack/sdp/sdpserv.c.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-15840" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-15840</a><br>TP-Link TL-WR840N devices allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (networking outage) via fragmented packets, as demonstrated by an “nmap -f” command.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18766" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18766</a><br>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the Call Dispatcher in Provisio SiteKiosk before 9.7.4905.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19201" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19201</a><br>A reflected XSS vulnerability in the ModCP Profile Editor in MyBB before 1.8.20 allows remote attackers to inject JavaScript via the ‘username’ parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18105" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18105</a><br>The console login resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers, who have previously obtained a user’s JSESSIONID cookie, to gain access to some of the built-in and potentially third party rest resources via a session fixation vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18106" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18106</a><br>The identifier_hash for a session token in Atlassian Crowd before version 2.9.1 could potentially collide with an identifier_hash for another user or a user in a different directory, this allows remote attackers who can authenticate to Crowd or an application using Crowd for authentication to gain access to another user’s session provided they can make their identifier hash collide with another user’s session identifier hash.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18108" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18108</a><br>The administration SMTP configuration resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 2.10.2 allows remote attackers with administration rights to execute arbitrary code via a JNDI injection.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18109" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18109</a><br>The login resource of CrowdId in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18110" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18110</a><br>The administration backup restore resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers to read files from the filesystem via a XXE vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18111" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18111</a><br>The OAuthHelper in Atlassian Application Links before version 5.0.10, from version 5.1.0 before version 5.1.3, and from version 5.2.0 before version 5.2.6 used an XML document builder that was vulnerable to XXE when consuming a client OAuth request. This allowed malicious oauth application linked applications to probe internal network resources by requesting internal locations, read the contents of files and also cause an out of memory exception affecting availability via an XML External Entity vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10269" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10269</a><br>BWA (aka Burrow-Wheeler Aligner) before 2019-01-23 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the bns_restore function in bntseq.c via a long sequence name in a .alt file.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10276" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10276</a><br>Western Bridge Cobub Razor 0.8.0 has a file upload vulnerability via the web/assets/swf/uploadify.php URI, as demonstrated by a .php file with the image/jpeg content type.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10477" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10477</a><br>The FusionInventory plugin before 1.4 for GLPI 9.3.x and before 1.1 for GLPI 9.4.x mishandles sendXML actions.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10644" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10644</a><br>An issue was discovered in HYBBS 2.2. /?admin/user.html has a CSRF vulnerability that can add an administrator account.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10646" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10646</a><br>Wolf CMS v0.8.3.1 is affected by cross site scripting (XSS) in the module Add Snippet (/?/admin/snippet/add). This allows an attacker to insert arbitrary JavaScript as user input, which will be executed whenever the affected snippet is loaded.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9605&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9605&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHP Scripts Ma
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.28</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-28/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-28/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.818Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.817Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9864" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9864</a><br>PHP Scripts Mall Amazon Affiliate Store 2.1.6 allows Parameter Tampering of the payment amount.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6542" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6542</a><br>ENTTEC Datagate MK2, Storm 24, Pixelator all firmware versions prior to (70044,70050,70060)_update_05032019-482 allows an unauthenticated user to initiate a remote reboot, which may be used to cause a denial of service condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6602" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6602</a><br>In BIG-IP 11.5.1-11.5.8 and 11.6.1-11.6.3, the Configuration Utility login page may not follow best security practices when handling a malicious request.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6603" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6603</a><br>In BIG-IP 11.5.1-11.5.8, 11.6.1-11.6.3, 12.1.0-12.1.3, and 13.0.0-13.0.1, malformed TCP packets sent to a self IP address or a FastL4 virtual server may cause an interruption of service. The control plane is not exposed to this issue. This issue impacts the data plane virtual servers and self IPs.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6604" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6604</a><br>On BIG-IP 11.5.1-11.5.8, 11.6.1-11.6.3, 12.1.0-12.1.3.6, 13.0.0-13.1.1.1, and 14.0.0-14.0.0.2, under certain conditions, hardware systems with a High-Speed Bridge and using non-default Layer 2 forwarding configurations may experience a lockup of the High-Speed Bridge.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6605" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6605</a><br>On BIG-IP 11.5.1-11.5.8, 11.6.1-11.6.3, and 12.0.x, an undisclosed sequence of packets received by an SSL virtual server and processed by an associated Client SSL or Server SSL profile may cause a denial of service.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6606" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6606</a><br>On BIG-IP 11.5.1-11.6.3.4, 12.1.0-12.1.3.7, 13.0.0-13.1.1.3, and 14.0.0-14.0.0.2, when processing certain SNMP requests with a request-id of 0, the snmpd process may leak a small amount of memory.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6607" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6607</a><br>On BIG-IP ASM 11.5.1-11.5.8, 11.6.1-11.6.3, 12.1.0-12.1.3, 13.0.0-13.1.1.3, and 14.0.0-14.0.0.2, there is a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in an ASM violation viewed in the Configuration utility. In the worst case, an attacker can store a CSRF which results in code execution as the admin user.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6608" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6608</a><br>On BIG-IP 11.5.1-11.6.3, 12.1.0-12.1.3, 13.0.0-13.1.1.1, and 14.0.0-14.0.0.2, under certain conditions, the snmpd daemon may leak memory on a multi-blade BIG-IP vCMP guest when processing authorized SNMP requests.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7251" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7251</a><br>An Integer Signedness issue (for a return code) in the res_pjsip_sdp_rtp module in Digium Asterisk versions 15.7.1 and earlier and 16.1.1 and earlier allows remote authenticated users to crash Asterisk via a specially crafted SDP protocol violation.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7524" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7524</a><br>In Dovecot before 2.2.36.3 and 2.3.x before 2.3.5.1, a local attacker can cause a buffer overflow in the indexer-worker process, which can be used to elevate to root. This occurs because of missing checks in the fts and pop3-uidl components.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9164" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9164</a><br>Command injection in Nagios XI before 5.5.11 allows an authenticated users to execute arbitrary remote commands via a new autodiscovery job.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9165" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9165</a><br>SQL injection vulnerability in Nagios XI before 5.5.11 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the API when using fusekeys and malicious user id.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9166" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9166</a><br>Privilege escalation in Nagios XI before 5.5.11 allows local attackers to elevate privileges to root via write access to config.inc.php and import_xiconfig.php.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9167" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9167</a><br>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Nagios XI before 5.5.11 allows attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the xiwindow parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9202" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9202</a><br>Nagios IM (component of Nagios XI) before 2.2.7 allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary code via API key issues.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9203" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9203</a><br>Authorization bypass in Nagios IM (component of Nagios XI) before 2.2.7 allows closing incidents in IM via the API.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9204" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9204</a><br>SQL injection vulnerability in Nagios IM (component of Nagios XI) before 2.2.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3869" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3869</a><br>When running Tower before 3.4.3 on OpenShift or Kubernetes, application credentials are exposed to playbook job runs via environment variables. A malicious user with the ability to write playbooks could use this to gain administrative privileges.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5674" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5674</a><br>NVIDIA GeForce Experience before 3.18 contains a vulnerability when ShadowPlay or GameStream is enabled. When an attacker has access to the system and creates a hard link, the software does not check for hard link attacks. This behavior may lead to code execution, denial of service, or escalation of privileges.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5737" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5737</a><br>An attacker can cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by establishing an HTTP or HTTPS connection in keep-alive mode and by sending headers very slowly thereby keeping the connection and associated resources alive for a long period of time. Attack potential is mitigated by the use of a load balancer or other proxy layer. This vulnerability is an extension of CVE-2018-12121, addressed in November and impacts all active release lines including 6, 8, 10 and 11.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5739" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5739</a><br>Keep-alive HTTP and HTTPS connections can remain open and inactive for up to 2 minutes in Node.js 6.16.0 and earlier. Node.js 8.0.0 introduced a dedicated server.keepAliveTimeout which defaults to 5 seconds. The behavior in Node.js 6.16.0 and earlier is a potential Denial of Service (DoS) attack vector. Node.js 6.17.0 introduces server.keepAliveTimeout and the 5-second default.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-20678" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-20678</a><br>LibreNMS through 1.47 allows SQL injection via the html/ajax_table.php sort[hostname] parameter, exploitable by authenticated users during a search.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0212" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0212</a><br>In all previously released Apache HBase 2.x versions (2.0.0-2.0.4, 2.1.0-2.1.3), authorization was incorrectly applied to users of the HBase REST server. Requests sent to the HBase REST server were executed with the permissions of the REST server itself, not with the permissions of the end-user. This issue is only relevant when HBase is configured with Kerberos authentication, HBase authorization is enabled, and the REST server is configured with SPNEGO authentication. This issue does not extend beyond the HBase REST server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0222" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0222</a><br>In Apache ActiveMQ 5.0.0 - 5.15.8, unmarshalling corrupt MQTT frame can lead to broker Out of Memory exception making it unresponsive.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0224" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0224</a><br>In Apache JSPWiki 2.9.0 to 2.11.0.M2, a carefully crafted URL could execute javascript on another user’s session. No information could be saved on the server or jspwiki database, nor would an attacker be able to execute js on someone else’s browser; only on its own browser.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0225" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0225</a><br>A specially crafted url could be used to access files under the ROOT directory of the application on Apache JSPWiki 2.9.0 to 2.11.0.M2, which could be used by an attacker to obtain registered users’ details.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3710" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3710</a><br>Dell Networking OS10 has been updated to address a vulnerability which may be potentially exploited to compromise the system.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-16529" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-16529</a><br>A password reset vulnerability has been discovered in Forcepoint Email Security 8.5.x. The password reset URL can be used after the intended expiration period or after the URL has already been used to reset a password.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19879" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19879</a><br>An issue was discovered in /cgi-bin/luci on Teltonika RTU9XX (e.g., RUT950) R_31.04.89 before R_00.05.00.5 devices. The authentication functionality is not protected from automated tools used to make login attempts to the application. An anonymous attacker has the ability to make unlimited login attempts with an automated tool. This ability could lead to cracking a targeted user’s password.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-20144" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-20144</a><br>GitLab Community and Enterprise Edition 11.x before 11.3.13, 11.4.x before 11.4.11, and 11.5.x before 11.5.4 has Incorrect Access Control.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18365" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18365</a><br>The Management Console in GitHub Enterprise 2.8.x before 2.8.7 has a deserialization issue that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. This occurs because the enterprise session secret is always the same, and can be found in the product’s source code. By sending a crafted cookie signed with this secret, one can call Marshal.load with arbitrary data, which is a problem because the Marshal data format allows Ruby objects.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-6330" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-6330</a><br>Laravel 5.4.15 is vulnerable to Error based SQL injection in save.php via dhx_user and dhx_version parameters.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003040" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003040</a><br>A sandbox bypass vulnerability in Jenkins Script Security Plugin 1.55 and earlier allows attackers to invoke arbitrary constructors in sandboxed scripts.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003041" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003041</a><br>A sandbox bypass vulnerability in Jenkins Pipeline: Groovy Plugin 2.64 and earlier allows attackers to invoke arbitrary constructors in sandboxed scripts.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003042" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003042</a><br>A cross site scripting vulnerability in Jenkins Lockable Resources Plugin 2.4 and earlier allows attackers able to control resource names to inject arbitrary JavaScript in web pages rendered by the plugin.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003043" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003043</a><br>A missing permission check in Jenkins Slack Notification Plugin 2.19 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to connect to an attacker-specified URL using attacker-specified credentials IDs obtained through another method, capturing credentials stored in Jenkins.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003044" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003044</a><br>A cross-site request forgery vulnerability in Jenkins Slack Notification Plugin 2.19 and earlier allows attackers to connect to an attacker-specified URL using attacker-specified credentials IDs obtained through another method, capturing credentials stored in Jenkins.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003045" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003045</a><br>A vulnerability in Jenkins ECS Publisher Plugin 1.0.0 and earlier allows attackers with Item/Extended Read permission, or local file system access to the Jenkins home directory to obtain the API token configured in this plugin’s configuration.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003046" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003046</a><br>A cross-site request forgery vulnerability in Jenkins Fortify on Demand Uploader Plugin 3.0.10 and earlier allows attackers to initiate a connection to an attacker-specified server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003047" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003047</a><br>A missing permission check in Jenkins Fortify on Demand Uploader Plugin 3.0.10 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to initiate a connection to an attacker-specified server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1003048" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1003048</a><br>A vulnerability in Jenkins PRQA Plugin 3.1.0 and earlier allows attackers with local file system access to the Jenkins home directory to obtain the unencrypted password from the plugin configuration.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10250" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10250</a><br>UCWeb UC Browser 7.0.185.1002 on Windows uses HTTP for downloading certain PDF modules, which allows MITM attacks.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10251" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10251</a><br>The UCWeb UC Browser application through 2019-03-26 for Android uses HTTP to download certain modules associated with PDF and Microsoft Office files (related to libpicsel), which allows MITM attacks.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10254" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10254</a><br>In MISP before 2.4.105, the app/View/Layouts/default.ctp default layout template has a Reflected XSS vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10255" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10255</a><br>An Open Redirect vulnerability for all browsers in Jupyter Notebook before 5.7.7 and some browsers (Chrome, Firefox) in JupyterHub before 0.9.5 allows crafted links to the login page, which will redirect to a malicious site after successful login. Servers running on a base_url prefix are not affected.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10260" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10260</a><br>Total.js CMS 12.0.0 has XSS related to themes/admin/views/index.html (item.message) and themes/admin/public/ui.js (column.format).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10262" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10262</a><br>A SQL Injection issue was discovered in BlueCMS 1.6. The variable $ad_id is spliced directly in uploads/admin/ad.php in the admin folder, and is not wrapped in single quotes, resulting in injection around the escape of magic quotes.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9864&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9864&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHP Scripts Ma
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.27</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-27/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-27/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.816Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.813Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9860" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9860</a><br>Due to unencrypted signal communication and predictability of rolling codes, an attacker can “desynchronize” an ABUS Secvest wireless remote control (FUBE50014 or FUBE50015) relative to its controlled Secvest wireless alarm system FUAA50000 3.01.01, so that sent commands by the remote control are not accepted anymore.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9862" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9862</a><br>An issue was discovered on ABUS Secvest wireless alarm system FUAA50000 3.01.01 in conjunction with Secvest remote control FUBE50014 or FUBE50015. Because “encrypted signal transmission” is missing, an attacker is able to eavesdrop sensitive data as cleartext (for instance, the current rolling code state).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9863" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9863</a><br>Due to the use of an insecure algorithm for rolling codes in the ABUS Secvest wireless alarm system FUAA50000 3.01.01 and its remote controls FUBE50014 and FUBE50015, an attacker is able to predict valid future rolling codes, and can thus remotely control the alarm system in an unauthorized way.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3814" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3814</a><br>It was discovered that Dovecot before versions 2.2.36.1 and 2.3.4.1 incorrectly handled client certificates. A remote attacker in possession of a valid certificate with an empty username field could possibly use this issue to impersonate other users.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3821" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3821</a><br>A flaw was found in the way civetweb frontend was handling requests for ceph RGW server with SSL enabled. An unauthenticated attacker could create multiple connections to ceph RADOS gateway to exhaust file descriptors for ceph-radosgw service resulting in a remote denial of service.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3828" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3828</a><br>Ansible fetch module before versions 2.5.15, 2.6.14, 2.7.8 has a path traversal vulnerability which allows copying and overwriting files outside of the specified destination in the local ansible controller host, by not restricting an absolute path.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3829" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3829</a><br>A vulnerability was found in gnutls versions from 3.5.8 before 3.6.7. A memory corruption (double free) vulnerability in the certificate verification API. Any client or server application that verifies X.509 certificates with GnuTLS 3.5.8 or later is affected.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3847" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3847</a><br>A vulnerability was found in moodle before versions 3.6.3, 3.5.5, 3.4.8 and 3.1.17. Users with the “login as other users” capability (such as administrators/managers) can access other users’ Dashboards, but the JavaScript those other users may have added to their Dashboard was not being escaped when being viewed by the user logging in on their behalf.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3877" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3877</a><br>A vulnerability was found in mod_auth_mellon before v0.14.2. An open redirect in the logout URL allows requests with backslashes to pass through by assuming that it is a relative URL, while the browsers silently convert backslash characters into forward slashes treating them as an absolute URL. This mismatch allows an attacker to bypass the redirect URL validation logic in apr_uri_parse function.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5418" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5418</a><br>There is a File Content Disclosure vulnerability in Action View (Rails) &lt;5.2.2.1, &lt;5.1.6.2, &lt;5.0.7.2, &lt;4.2.11.1 where specially crafted accept headers can cause contents of arbitrary files on the target system’s filesystem to be exposed.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5419" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5419</a><br>There is a possible denial of service vulnerability in Action View (Rails) &lt;5.2.2.1, &lt;5.1.6.2, &lt;5.0.7.2, &lt;4.2.11.1 where specially crafted accept headers can cause action view to consume 100% cpu and make the server unresponsive.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5420" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5420</a><br>A remote code execution vulnerability in development mode Rails &lt;5.2.2.1, &lt;6.0.0.beta3 can allow an attacker to guess the automatically generated development mode secret token. This secret token can be used in combination with other Rails internals to escalate to a remote code execution exploit.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6536" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6536</a><br>Opening a specially crafted LCDS LAquis SCADA before 4.3.1.71 ELS file may result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer, which may allow an attacker to execute remote code in the context of the current process.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0160" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0160</a><br>Buffer overflow in system firmware for EDK II may allow unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege and/or denial of service via network access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0161" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0161</a><br>Stack overflow in XHCI for EDK II may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1737" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1737</a><br>A vulnerability in the processing of IP Service Level Agreement (SLA) packets by Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an interface wedge and an eventual denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper socket resources handling in the IP SLA responder application code. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IP SLA packets to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause an interface to become wedged, resulting in an eventual denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1738" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1738</a><br>A vulnerability in the Network-Based Application Recognition (NBAR) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to a parsing issue on DNS packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted DNS packets through routers that are running an affected version and have NBAR enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1739" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1739</a><br>A vulnerability in the Network-Based Application Recognition (NBAR) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to a parsing issue on DNS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DNS packets through routers that are running an affected version and have NBAR enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1740" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1740</a><br>A vulnerability in the Network-Based Application Recognition (NBAR) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability are due to a parsing issue on DNS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DNS packets through routers that are running an affected version and have NBAR enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1741" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1741</a><br>A vulnerability in the Cisco Encrypted Traffic Analytics (ETA) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that exists when handling a malformed incoming packet, leading to access to an internal data structure after it has been freed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted, malformed IP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1742" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1742</a><br>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive configuration information. The vulnerability is due to improper access control to files within the web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive configuration information.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1743" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1743</a><br>A vulnerability in the web UI framework of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to make unauthorized changes to the filesystem of the affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious file and uploading it to the device. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain elevated privileges on the affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1745" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1745</a><br>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected commands. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges on the affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1746" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1746</a><br>A vulnerability in the Cluster Management Protocol (CMP) processing code in Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation when processing CMP management packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious CMP management packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause the switch to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. The switch will reload automatically.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1747" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1747</a><br>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Short Message Service (SMS) handling functionality of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of SMS protocol data units (PDUs) that are encoded with a special character set. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious SMS message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless WAN (WWAN) cellular interface module on an affected device to crash, resulting in a DoS condition that would require manual intervention to restore normal operating conditions.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1748" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1748</a><br>A vulnerability in the Cisco Network Plug-and-Play (PnP) agent of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. The vulnerability exists because the affected software insufficiently validates certificates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt and modify confidential information on user connections to the affected software.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1749" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1749</a><br>A vulnerability in the ingress traffic validation of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Aggregation Services Router (ASR) 900 Route Switch Processor 3 (RSP3) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the software insufficiently validates ingress traffic on the ASIC used on the RSP3 platform. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the iosd process, triggering a reload of the affected device and resulting in a DoS condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1750" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1750</a><br>A vulnerability in the Easy Virtual Switching System (VSS) of Cisco IOS XE Software on Catalyst 4500 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the switches to reload. The vulnerability is due to incomplete error handling when processing Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) packets used with the Easy Virtual Switching System. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted CDP packet. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1751" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1751</a><br>A vulnerability in the Network Address Translation 64 (NAT64) functions of Cisco IOS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause either an interface queue wedge or a device reload. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of certain IPv4 packet streams that are sent through the device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IPv4 packet streams through the device. An exploit could allow the attacker to either cause an interface queue wedge or a device reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1752" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1752</a><br>A vulnerability in the ISDN functions of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of specific values in the Q.931 information elements. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by calling the affected device with specific Q.931 information elements being present. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1753" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1753</a><br>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated but unprivileged (level 1), remote attacker to run privileged Cisco IOS commands by using the web UI. The vulnerability is due to a failure to validate and sanitize input in Web Services Management Agent (WSMA) functions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a malicious payload to the affected device’s web UI. A successful exploit could allow the lower-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary commands with higher privileges on the affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1754" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1754</a><br>A vulnerability in the authorization subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated but unprivileged (level 1), remote attacker to run privileged Cisco IOS commands by using the web UI. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user privileges of web UI users. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a malicious payload to a specific endpoint in the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the lower-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary commands with higher privileges on the affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1755" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1755</a><br>A vulnerability in the Web Services Management Agent (WSMA) function of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary Cisco IOS commands as a privilege level 15 user. The vulnerability occurs because the affected software improperly sanitizes user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted HTTP requests to the targeted application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1756" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1756</a><br>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability occurs because the affected software improperly sanitizes user-supplied input. An attacker who has valid administrator access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a username with a malicious payload in the web UI and subsequently making a request to a specific endpoint in the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands as the root user, allowing complete compromise of the system.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1757" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1757</a><br>A vulnerability in the Cisco Smart Call Home feature of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data using an invalid certificate. The vulnerability is due to insufficient certificate validation by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt confidential information on user connections to the affected software.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1758" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1758</a><br>A vulnerability in 802.1x function of Cisco IOS Software on the Catalyst 6500 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to access the network prior to authentication. The vulnerability is due to how the 802.1x packets are handled in the process path. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to connect to the network on an 802.1x configured port. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to intermittently obtain access to the network.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1759" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1759</a><br>A vulnerability in access control list (ACL) functionality of the Gigabit Ethernet Management interface of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to reach the configured IP addresses on the Gigabit Ethernet Management interface. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that was introduced in the Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.1 Release, which prevents the ACL from working when applied against the management interface. An attacker could exploit this issue by attempting to access the device via the management interface.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1760" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1760</a><br>A vulnerability in Performance Routing Version 3 (PfRv3) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to the processing of malformed smart probe packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted smart probe packets at the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reload the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) attack on an affected system.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1761" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1761</a><br>A vulnerability in the Hot Standby Router Protocol (HSRP) subsystem of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to receive potentially sensitive information from an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient memory initialization. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by receiving HSRPv2 traffic from an adjacent HSRP member. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to receive potentially sensitive information from the adjacent device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1762" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1762</a><br>A vulnerability in the Secure Storage feature of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive system information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper memory operations performed at encryption time, when affected software handles configuration updates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by retrieving the contents of specific memory locations of an affected device. A successful exploit could result in the disclosure of keying materials that are part of the device configuration, which can be used to recover critical system information.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12545" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12545</a><br>In Eclipse Jetty version 9.3.x and 9.4.x, the server is vulnerable to Denial of Service conditions if a remote client sends either large SETTINGs frames container containing many settings, or many small SETTINGs frames. The vulnerability is due to the additional CPU and memory allocations required to handle changed settings.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12546" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12546</a><br>In Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.0 to 1.5.5 (inclusive) when a client publishes a retained message to a topic, then has its access to that topic revoked, the retained message will still be published to clients that subscribe to that topic in the future. In some applications this may result in clients being able cause effects that would otherwise not be allowed.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12550" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12550</a><br>When Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.0 to 1.5.5 (inclusive) is configured to use an ACL file, and that ACL file is empty, or contains only comments or blank lines, then Mosquitto will treat this as though no ACL file has been defined and use a default allow policy. The new behaviour is to have an empty ACL file mean that all access is denied, which is not a useful configuration but is not unexpected.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12551" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12551</a><br>When Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.0 to 1.5.5 (inclusive) is configured to use a password file for authentication, any malformed data in the password file will be treated as valid. This typically means that the malformed data becomes a username and no password. If this occurs, clients can circumvent authentication and get access to the broker by using the malformed username. In particular, a blank line will be treated as a valid empty username. Other security measures are unaffected. Users who have only used the mosquitto_passwd utility to create and modify their password files are unaffected by this vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-14814" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-14814</a><br>WECON Technology PI Studio HMI versions 4.1.9 and prior and PI Studio versions 4.2.34 and prior lacks proper validation of user-supplied data, which may result in a read past the end of an allocated object.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-15585" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-15585</a><br>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in newwinform.php in GNUBOARD5 before 5.3.1.6 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the popup title parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18994" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18994</a><br>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 allows an out of bounds read when opening a specially crafted project file, which may cause a system crash or allow data exfiltration.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19016" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19016</a><br>Rockwell Automation EtherNet/IP Web Server Modules 1756-EWEB (includes 1756-EWEBK) Version 5.001 and earlier, and CompactLogix 1768-EWEB Version 2.005 and earlier. A remote attacker could send a crafted UDP packet to the SNMP service causing a denial-of-service condition to occur until the affected product is restarted.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19466" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19466</a><br>A vulnerability was found in Portainer before 1.20.0. Portainer stores LDAP credentials, corresponding to a master password, in cleartext and allows their retrieval via API calls.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19641" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19641</a><br>Unauthenticated remote code execution issue in Micro Focus Solutions Business Manager (SBM) (formerly Serena Business Manager (SBM)) versions prior to 11.5.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19642" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19642</a><br>Denial of service issue in Micro Focus Solutions Business Manager (SBM) (formerly Serena Business Manager (SBM)) versions prior to 11.5.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19643" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19643</a><br>Information leakage issue in Micro Focus Solutions Business Manager (SBM) (formerly Serena Business Manager (SBM)) versions prior to 11.5.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19644" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19644</a><br>Reflected cross site script issue in Micro Focus Solutions Business Manager (SBM) (formerly Serena Business Manager (SBM)) versions prior to 11.5.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19648" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19648</a><br>An issue was discovered in ADTRAN PMAA 1.6.2-1, 1.6.3, and 1.6.4. NETCONF Access Management (NACM) allows unprivileged users to create privileged users and execute arbitrary commands via the use of the diagnostic-profile over RESTCONF.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-18364" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-18364</a><br>phpFK lite has XSS via the faq.php, members.php, or search.php query string or the user.php user parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-10934" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-10934</a><br>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in the JBoss Management Console versions before 7.1.6.CR1, 7.1.6.GA. Users with roles that can create objects in the application can exploit this to attack other privileged users.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12178" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12178</a><br>Buffer overflow in network stack for EDK II may allow unprivileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege and/or denial of service via network.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12179" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12179</a><br>Improper configuration in system firmware for EDK II may allow unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege, information disclosure and/or denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12180" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12180</a><br>Buffer overflow in BlockIo service for EDK II may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege, information disclosure and/or denial of service via network access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12181" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12181</a><br>Stack overflow in corrupted bmp for EDK II may allow unprivileged user to potentially enable denial of service or elevation of privilege via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12182" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12182</a><br>Insufficient memory write check in SMM service for EDK II may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege, information disclosure and/or denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12183" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12183</a><br>Stack overflow in DxeCore for EDK II may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege, information disclosure and/or denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-3613" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-3613</a><br>Logic issue in variable service module for EDK II/UDK2018/UDK2017/UDK2015 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege, information disclosure and/or denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-5923" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-5923</a><br>In HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP PageWide Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed, and HP OfficeJet Enterprise Printers, solution application signature checking may allow potential execution of arbitrary code.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-5926" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-5926</a><br>A potential vulnerability has been identified in HP Remote Graphics Software?s certificate authentication process version 7.5.0 and earlier.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-5927" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-5927</a><br>HP Support Assistant before 8.7.50.3 allows an unauthorized person with local access to load arbitrary code.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-2748" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-2748</a><br>A potential security vulnerability caused by the use of insecure (http) transactions during login has been identified with early versions of the Isaac Mizrahi Smartwatch mobile app. HP has no access to customer data as a result of this issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-2752" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-2752</a><br>A potential security vulnerability caused by incomplete obfuscation of application configuration information was discovered in Tommy Hilfiger TH24/7 Android app versions 2.0.0.11, 2.0.1.14, 2.1.0.16, and 2.2.0.19. HP has no access to customer data as a result of this issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-7655" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-7655</a><br>In Eclipse Mosquitto version from 1.0 to 1.4.15, a Null Dereference vulnerability was found in the Mosquitto library which could lead to crashes for those applications using the library.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-9626" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-9626</a><br>Systems using the Marel Food Processing Systems Pluto platform do not restrict remote access. Marel has created an update for Pluto-based applications. This update will restrict remote access by implementing SSH authentication.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1000031" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1000031</a><br>A disk space or quota exhaustion issue exists in article2pdf_getfile.php in the article2pdf Wordpress plugin 0.24, 0.25, 0.26, 0.27. Visiting PDF generation link but not following the redirect will leave behind a PDF file on disk which will never be deleted by the plug-in.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1010257" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1010257</a><br>An Information Disclosure / Data Modification issue exists in article2pdf_getfile.php in the article2pdf Wordpress plugin 0.24, 0.25, 0.26, 0.27. A URL can be constructed which allows overriding the PDF file’s path leading to any PDF whose path is known and which is readable to the web server can be downloaded. The file will be deleted after download if the web server has permission to do so. For PHP versions before 5.3, any file can be read by null terminating the string left of the file extension.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10124" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10124</a><br>An issue was discovered in the hwpoison implementation in mm/memory-failure.c in the Linux kernel before 5.0.4. When soft_offline_in_use_page() runs on a thp tail page after pmd is split, an attacker can cause a denial of service (BUG).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10125" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10125</a><br>An issue was discovered in aio_poll() in fs/aio.c in the Linux kernel through 5.0.4. A file may be released by aio_poll_wake() if an expected event is triggered immediately (e.g., by the close of a pair of pipes) after the return of vfs_poll(), and this will cause a use-after-free.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10231" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10231</a><br>Teclib GLPI before 9.4.1.1 is affected by a PHP type juggling vulnerability allowing bypass of authentication. This occurs in Auth::checkPassword() (inc/auth.class.php).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10232" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10232</a><br>Teclib GLPI through 9.3.3 has SQL injection via the “cycle” parameter in /scripts/unlock_tasks.php.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10233" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10233</a><br>Teclib GLPI before 9.4.1.1 is affected by a timing attack associated with a cookie.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10237" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10237</a><br>S-CMS PHP v1.0 has a CSRF vulnerability to add a new admin user via the 4.edu.php/admin/ajax.php?type=admin&amp;action=add&amp;lang=0 URI, a related issue to CVE-2019-9040.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10238" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10238</a><br>Sitemagic CMS v4.4 has XSS in SMFiles/FrmUpload.class.php via the filename parameter.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9860&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9860&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Due to unencry
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.26</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-26/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-26/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.814Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.809Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9743" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9743</a><br>An issue was discovered on PHOENIX CONTACT RAD-80211-XD and RAD-80211-XD/HP-BUS devices. Command injection can occur in the WebHMI component.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9744" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9744</a><br>An issue was discovered on PHOENIX CONTACT FL NAT SMCS 8TX, FL NAT SMN 8TX, FL NAT SMN 8TX-M, and FL NAT SMN 8TX-M-DMG devices. There is unauthorized access to the WEB-UI by attackers arriving from the same source IP address as an authenticated user, because this IP address is used as a session identifier.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9764" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9764</a><br>HashiCorp Consul 1.4.3 lacks server hostname verification for agent-to-agent TLS communication. In other words, the product behaves as if verify_server_hostname were set to false, even when it is actually set to true. This is fixed in 1.4.4.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9961" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9961</a><br>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ressource view in core/modules/resource/RESOURCEVIEW.php in Wikindx prior to version 5.7.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the id parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6540" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6540</a><br>The Conexus telemetry protocol utilized within Medtronic MyCareLink Monitor versions 24950 and 24952, CareLink Monitor version 2490C, CareLink 2090 Programmer, Amplia CRT-D, Claria CRT-D, Compia CRT-D, Concerto CRT-D, Concerto II CRT-D, Consulta CRT-D, Evera ICD, Maximo II CRT-D and ICD, Mirro ICD, Nayamed ND ICD, Primo ICD, Protecta ICD and CRT-D, Secura ICD, Virtuoso ICD, Virtuoso II ICD, Visia AF ICD, and Viva CRT-D does not implement encryption. An attacker with adjacent short-range access to a target product can listen to communications, including the transmission of sensitive data.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6569" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6569</a><br>A vulnerability has been identified in Scalance X-200 (All versions), Scalance X-300 (All versions), Scalance XP/XC/XF-200 (All versions &lt;V4.1). The monitor barrier of the affected products insufficiently blocks data from being forwarded over the mirror port into the mirrored network. An attacker might use this behaviour to transmit malicious packets to systems in the mirrored network, possibly influencing their configuration and runtime behaviour. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the traffic-receiving network. Successful exploitation requires no system privileges and no user interaction. An attacker could use the vulnerability to compromise the confidentiality and availablity of the traffic-generating network. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7167" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7167</a><br>Zcash, before the Sapling network upgrade (2018-10-28), had a counterfeiting vulnerability. A key-generation process, during evaluation of polynomials related to a to-be-proven statement, produced certain bypass elements. Availability of these elements allowed a cheating prover to bypass a consistency check, and consequently transform the proof of one statement into an ostensibly valid proof of a different statement, thereby breaking the soundness of the proof system. This misled the original Sprout zk-SNARK verifier into accepting the correctness of a transaction.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-8987" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-8987</a><br>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user to gain access to all the capabilities of the web interface available to more privileged users. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-8988" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-8988</a><br>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a persistent cross-site contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a user to escalate their privileges on the affected system, in a way that may allow for data modifications and deletions that should be denied. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-8989" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-8989</a><br>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a vulnerability that theoretically enables a user to spoof their account to look like a different user in the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9053" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9053</a><br>An issue was discovered in CMS Made Simple 2.2.8. It is possible with the News module, through a crafted URL, to achieve unauthenticated blind time-based SQL injection via the m1_idlist parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3804" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3804</a><br>It was found that cockpit before version 184 used glib’s base64 decode functionality incorrectly resulting in a denial of service attack. An unauthenticated attacker could send a specially crafted request with an invalid base64-encoded cookie which could cause the web service to crash.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3826" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3826</a><br>A stored, DOM based, cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw was found in Prometheus before version 2.7.1. An attacker could exploit this by convincing an authenticated user to visit a crafted URL on a Prometheus server, allowing for the execution and persistent storage of arbitrary scripts.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3830" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3830</a><br>A vulnerability was found in ceilometer before version 12.0.0.0rc1. An Information Exposure in ceilometer-agent prints sensitive configuration data to log files without DEBUG logging being activated.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3848" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3848</a><br>A vulnerability was found in moodle before versions 3.6.3, 3.5.5 and 3.4.8. Permissions were not correctly checked before loading event information into the calendar’s edit event modal popup, so logged in non-guest users could view unauthorised calendar events. (Note: It was read-only access, users could not edit the events.)<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3849" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3849</a><br>A vulnerability was found in moodle before versions 3.6.3, 3.5.5 and 3.4.8. Users could assign themselves an escalated role within courses or content accessed via LTI, by modifying the request to the LTI publisher site.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3878" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3878</a><br>A vulnerability was found in mod_auth_mellon before v0.14.2. If Apache is configured as a reverse proxy and mod_auth_mellon is configured to only let through authenticated users (with the require valid-user directive), adding special HTTP headers that are normally used to start the special SAML ECP (non-browser based) can be used to bypass authentication.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6341" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6341</a><br>In Drupal 7 versions prior to 7.65; Drupal 8.6 versions prior to 8.6.13;Drupal 8.5 versions prior to 8.5.14. Under certain circumstances the File module/subsystem allows a malicious user to upload a file that can trigger a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1572" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1572</a><br>PAN-OS 9.0.0 may allow an unauthenticated remote user to access php files.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3597" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3597</a><br>Authentication Bypass vulnerability in McAfee Network Security Manager (NSM) 9.1 &lt; 9.1.7.75.2 and 9.2 &lt; 9.2.7.31 (9.2 Update 2) allows unauthenticated users to gain administrator rights via incorrect handling of expired GUI sessions.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3606" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3606</a><br>Data Leakage Attacks vulnerability in the web portal component when in an MDR pair in McAfee Network Security Management (NSM) 9.1 &lt; 9.1.7.75 (Update 4) and 9.2 &lt; 9.2.7.31 Update2 allows administrators to view configuration information in plain text format via the GUI or GUI terminal commands.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-16856" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-16856</a><br>In a default Red Hat Openstack Platform Director installation, openstack-octavia before versions openstack-octavia 2.0.2-5 and openstack-octavia-3.0.1-0.20181009115732 creates log files that are readable by all users. Sensitive information such as private keys can appear in these log files allowing for information exposure.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19856" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19856</a><br>GitLab CE/EE before 11.3.12, 11.4.x before 11.4.10, and 11.5.x before 11.5.3 allows Directory Traversal in Templates API.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2010-5305" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2010-5305</a><br>The potential exists for exposure of the product’s password used to restrict unauthorized access to Rockwell PLC5/SLC5/0x/RSLogix 1785-Lx and 1747-L5x controllers. The potential exists for an unauthorized programming and configuration client to gain access to the product and allow changes to the product?s configuration or program. When applicable, upgrade product firmware to a version that includes enhanced security functionality compatible with Rockwell Automation’s FactoryTalk Security services.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2013-2805" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2013-2805</a><br>Rockwell Automation RSLinx Enterprise Software (LogReceiver.exe) CPR9, CPR9-SR1, CPR9-SR2, CPR9-SR3, CPR9-SR4, CPR9-SR5, CPR9-SR5.1, and CPR9-SR6 does not handle input correctly and results in a logic error if it receives a datagram with an incorrect value in the ?Record Data Size? field. By sending a datagram to the service over Port 4444/UDP with the ?Record Data Size? field modified to an oversized value, an attacker could cause an out-of-bounds read access violation that leads to a service crash. The service can be recovered with a manual reboot. The patches and details pertaining to this vulnerability can be found at the following Rockwell Automation Security Advisory link (login is required): <a href="https://rockwellautomation.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/537599" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://rockwellautomation.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/537599</a><br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2013-2806" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2013-2806</a><br>Rockwell Automation RSLinx Enterprise Software (LogReceiver.exe) CPR9, CPR9-SR1, CPR9-SR2, CPR9-SR3, CPR9-SR4, CPR9-SR5, CPR9-SR5.1, and CPR9-SR6 does not handle input correctly and results in a logic error if it calculates an incorrect value for the ?End of Current Record? field. By sending a datagram to the service over Port 4444/UDP with the ?Record Data Size? field modified to a specifically oversized value, the service will calculate an undersized value for the ?Total Record Size.? Then the service will calculate an incorrect value for the ?End of Current Record? field causing access violations that lead to a service crash. The service can be recovered with a manual reboot. The patches and details pertaining to these vulnerabilities can be found at the following Rockwell Automation security advisory link (login is required): <a href="https://rockwellautomation.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/537599" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://rockwellautomation.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/537599</a><br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2013-2807" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2013-2807</a><br>Rockwell Automation RSLinx Enterprise Software (LogReceiver.exe) CPR9, CPR9-SR1, CPR9-SR2, CPR9-SR3, CPR9-SR4, CPR9-SR5, CPR9-SR5.1, and CPR9-SR6 does not handle input correctly and results in a logic error if it calculates an incorrect value for the ?Total Record Size? field. By sending a datagram to the service over Port 4444/UDP with the ?Record Data Size? field modified to a specifically oversized value, the service will calculate an undersized value for the ?Total Record Size? that will cause an out-of-bounds read access violation that leads to a service crash. The service can be recovered with a manual reboot. The patches and details pertaining to these vulnerabilities can be found at the following Rockwell Automation Security Advisory link (login is required): <a href="https://rockwellautomation.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/537599" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://rockwellautomation.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/537599</a><br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-5431" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-5431</a><br>Baxter SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System version 6.05 (model 35700BAX) with wireless battery module (WBM) version 16 contains a hard-coded password, which provides access to basic biomedical information, limited device settings, and network configuration of the WBM, if connected. The hard-coded password may allow an attacker with physical access to the device to access management functions to make unauthorized configuration changes to biomedical settings such as turn on and off wireless connections and the phase-complete audible alarm that indicates the end of an infusion phase. Baxter has released a new version of the SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System, version 8, which incorporates hardware and software changes.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-5432" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-5432</a><br>Baxter SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System version 6.05 (model 35700BAX) with wireless battery module (WBM) version 16 is remotely accessible via Port 22/SSH without authentication. A remote attacker may be able to make unauthorized configuration changes to the WBM, as well as issue commands to access account credentials and shared keys. Baxter asserts that this vulnerability only allows access to features and functionality on the WBM and that the SIGMA Spectrum infusion pump cannot be controlled from the WBM. Baxter has released a new version of the SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System, Version 8, which incorporates hardware and software changes.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-5433" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-5433</a><br>An unauthenticated remote attacker may be able to execute commands to view wireless account credentials that are stored in cleartext on Baxter SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System version 6.05 (model 35700BAX) with wireless battery module (WBM) version 16, which may allow an attacker to gain access the host network. Baxter has released a new version of the SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System, Version 8, which incorporates hardware and software changes.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-5434" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-5434</a><br>Baxter SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System version 6.05 (model 35700BAX) with wireless battery module (WBM) version 16 has a default account with hard-coded credentials used with the FTP protocol. Baxter asserts no files can be transferred to or from the WBM using this account. Baxter has released a new version of the SIGMA Spectrum Infusion System, Version 8, which incorporates hardware and software changes.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10068" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10068</a><br>An issue was discovered in Kentico before 12.0.15. Due to a failure to validate security headers, it was possible for a specially crafted request to the staging service to bypass the initial authentication and proceed to deserialize user-controlled .NET object input. This deserialization then led to unauthenticated remote code execution on the server where the Kentico instance was hosted.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9743&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9743&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;An issue was d
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.25</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-25/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-25/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.812Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.809Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10011" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10011</a><br>ICS/StaticPages/AddTestUsers.aspx in Jenzabar JICS (aka Internet Campus Solution) before 2019-02-06 allows remote attackers to create an arbitrary number of accounts with a password of 1234.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10012" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10012</a><br>Jenzabar JICS (aka Internet Campus Solution) before 9 allows remote attackers to upload and execute arbitrary .aspx code by placing it in a ZIP archive and using the MoxieManager (for .NET) plugin before 2.1.4 in the moxiemanager directory within the installation folder ICS\ICS.NET\ICSFileServer.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10044" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10044</a><br>Telegram Desktop before 1.5.12 on Windows, and the Telegram applications for Android, iOS, and Linux, is vulnerable to an IDN homograph attack when displaying messages containing URLs. This occurs because the application produces a clickable link even if (for example) Latin and Cyrillic characters exist in the same domain name, and the available font has an identical representation of characters from different alphabets.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7642" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7642</a><br>D-Link routers with the mydlink feature have some web interfaces without authentication requirements. An attacker can remotely obtain users’ DNS query logs and login logs. Vulnerable targets include but are not limited to the latest firmware versions of DIR-817LW (A1-1.04), DIR-816L (B1-2.06), DIR-816 (B1-2.06?), DIR-850L (A1-1.09), and DIR-868L (A1-1.10).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3835" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3835</a><br>It was found that the superexec operator was available in the internal dictionary in ghostscript before 9.27. A specially crafted PostScript file could use this flaw in order to, for example, have access to the file system outside of the constrains imposed by -dSAFER.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3838" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3838</a><br>It was found that the forceput operator could be extracted from the DefineResource method in ghostscript before 9.27. A specially crafted PostScript file could use this flaw in order to, for example, have access to the file system outside of the constrains imposed by -dSAFER.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3841" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3841</a><br>Kubevirt/virt-cdi-importer, versions 1.4.0 to 1.5.3 inclusive, were reported to disable TLS certificate validation when importing data into PVCs from container registries. This could enable man-in-the-middle attacks between a container registry and the virt-cdi-component, leading to possible undetected tampering of trusted container image content.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3856" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3856</a><br>An integer overflow flaw, which could lead to an out of bounds write, was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way keyboard prompt requests are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to execute code on the client system when a user connects to the server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3857" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3857</a><br>An integer overflow flaw which could lead to an out of bounds write was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SSH_MSG_CHANNEL_REQUEST packets with an exit signal are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to execute code on the client system when a user connects to the server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3860" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3860</a><br>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SFTP packets with empty payloads are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3861" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3861</a><br>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SSH packets with a padding length value greater than the packet length are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3863" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3863</a><br>A flaw was found in libssh2 before 1.8.1. A server could send a multiple keyboard interactive response messages whose total length are greater than unsigned char max characters. This value is used as an index to copy memory causing in an out of bounds memory write error.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3874" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3874</a><br>The SCTP socket buffer used by a userspace application is not accounted by the cgroups subsystem. An attacker can use this flaw to cause a denial of service attack. Kernel 3.10.x and 4.18.x branches are believed to be vulnerable.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-4046" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-4046</a><br>IBM WebSphere Application Server 7.0, 8.0, 8.5, and 9.0 is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by improper handling of request headers. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause the consumption of Memory. IBM X-Force ID: 156242.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6538" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6538</a><br>The Conexus telemetry protocol utilized within Medtronic MyCareLink Monitor versions 24950 and 24952, CareLink Monitor version 2490C, CareLink 2090 Programmer, Amplia CRT-D, Claria CRT-D, Compia CRT-D, Concerto CRT-D, Concerto II CRT-D, Consulta CRT-D, Evera ICD, Maximo II CRT-D and ICD, Mirro ICD, Nayamed ND ICD, Primo ICD, Protecta ICD and CRT-D, Secura ICD, Virtuoso ICD, Virtuoso II ICD, Visia AF ICD, and Viva CRT-D does not implement authentication or authorization. An attacker with adjacent short-range access to an affected product, in situations where the product?s radio is turned on, can inject, replay, modify, and/or intercept data within the telemetry communication. This communication protocol provides the ability to read and write memory values to affected implanted cardiac devices; therefore, an attacker could exploit this communication protocol to change memory in the implanted cardiac device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0204" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0204</a><br>A specifically crafted Docker image running under the root user can overwrite the init helper binary of the container runtime and/or the command executor in Apache Mesos versions pre-1.4.x, 1.4.0 to 1.4.2, 1.5.0 to 1.5.2, 1.6.0 to 1.6.1, and 1.7.0 to 1.7.1. A malicious actor can therefore gain root-level code execution on the host.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-16838" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-16838</a><br>A flaw was found in sssd Group Policy Objects implementation. When the GPO is not readable by SSSD due to a too strict permission settings on the server side, SSSD will allow all authenticated users to login instead of denying access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-9187" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-9187</a><br>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in Honeywell Experion PKS all versions prior to R400.6, all versions prior to R410.6, and all versions prior to R430.2 modules, which could lead to possible remote code execution or denial of service. Honeywell strongly encourages and recommends all customers running unsupported versions of EKPS prior to R400 to upgrade to a supported version.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2014-9189" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2014-9189</a><br>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities were found in Honeywell Experion PKS all versions prior to R400.6, all versions prior to R410.6, and all versions prior to R430.2 modules that could lead to possible remote code execution, dynamic memory corruption, or denial of service. Honeywell strongly encourages and recommends all customers running unsupported versions of EKPS prior to R400 to upgrade to a supported version.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-1007" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-1007</a><br>A specially crafted configuration file could be used to cause a stack-based buffer overflow condition in the OPCTest.exe, which may allow remote code execution on Opto 22 PAC Project Professional versions prior to R9.4008, PAC Project Basic versions prior to R9.4008, PAC Display Basic versions prior to R9.4g, PAC Display Professional versions prior to R9.4g, OptoOPCServer version R9.4c and prior that were installed by PAC Project installer, versions prior to R9.4008, and OptoDataLink version R9.4d and prior that were installed by PAC Project installer, versions prior to R9.4008. Opto 22 suggests upgrading to the new product version as soon as possible.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-1012" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-1012</a><br>Wireless keys are stored in plain text on version 5 of the Hospira LifeCare PCA Infusion System. According to Hospira, version 3 of the LifeCare PCA Infusion System is not indicated for wireless use, is not shipped with wireless capabilities, and should not be modified to be used in a wireless capacity in a clinical setting. Hospira has developed a new version of the PCS Infusion System, version 7.0 that addresses the identified vulnerabilities. Version 7.0 has Port 20/FTP and Port 23/TELNET closed by default to prevent unauthorized access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-1014" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-1014</a><br>A successful exploit of these vulnerabilities requires the local user to load a crafted DLL file in the system directory on servers running Schneider Electric OFS v3.5 with version v7.40 of SCADA Expert Vijeo Citect/CitectSCADA, OFS v3.5 with version v7.30 of Vijeo Citect/CitectSCADA, and OFS v3.5 with version v7.20 of Vijeo Citect/CitectSCADA.. If the application attempts to open that file, the application could crash or allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code. Schneider Electric recommends vulnerable users upgrade the OFS to V3.5 and install the latest service pack (SP 6 or newer) for their associated version.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-3952" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-3952</a><br>Wireless keys are stored in plain text on Hospira Plum A+ Infusion System version 13.4 and prior, Plum A+3 Infusion System version 13.6 and prior, and Symbiq Infusion System, version 3.13 and prior. Hospira recommends that customers close Port 20/FTP and Port 23/TELNET on the affected devices. Hospira has also released the Plum 360 Infusion System which is not vulnerable to this issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-3953" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-3953</a><br>Hard-coded accounts may be used to access Hospira Plum A+ Infusion System version 13.4 and prior, Plum A+3 Infusion System version 13.6 and prior, and Symbiq Infusion System, version 3.13 and prior. Hospira recommends that customers close Port 20/FTP and Port 23/TELNET on the affected devices. Hospira has also released the Plum 360 Infusion System which is not vulnerable to this issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-3954" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-3954</a><br>Hospira Plum A+ Infusion System version 13.4 and prior, Plum A+3 Infusion System version 13.6 and prior, and Symbiq Infusion System, version 3.13 and prior give unauthenticated users root privileges on Port 23/TELNET by default. An unauthorized user could issue commands to the pump. Hospira recommends that customers close Port 23/TELNET on the affected devices. Hospira has also released the Plum 360 Infusion System which is not vulnerable to this issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-3956" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-3956</a><br>Hospira Plum A+ Infusion System version 13.4 and prior, Plum A+3 Infusion System version 13.6 and prior, and Symbiq Infusion System, version 3.13 and prior accept drug libraries, firmware updates, pump commands, and unauthorized configuration changes from unauthenticated devices on the host network. Hospira recommends that customers close Port 20/FTP and Port 23/TELNET on the affected devices. Hospira has also released the Plum 360 Infusion System which is not vulnerable to this issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-9362" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-9362</a><br>ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus before 9312 contains an XML injection at add Configuration items CMDB API.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-9376" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-9376</a><br>ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus before 9314 contains a local file inclusion vulnerability in the defModule parameter in DefaultConfigDef.do and AssetDefaultConfigDef.do.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10060" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10060</a><br>The Verix Multi-app Conductor application 2.7 for Verifone Verix suffers from a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a long configuration key value. An attacker must be able to download files to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10061" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-10061</a><br>utils/find-opencv.js in node-opencv (aka OpenCV bindings for Node.js) prior to 6.1.0 is vulnerable to Command Injection. It does not validate user input allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-10011&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-10011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICS/StaticPa
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.24</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-24/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-24/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.810Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.809Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9977" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9977</a><br>The renderer process in the entertainment system on Tesla Model 3 vehicles mishandles JIT compilation, which allows attackers to trigger firmware code execution, and display a crafted message to vehicle occupants.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9977&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9977&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;The renderer p
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.23</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-23/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-23/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.808Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.805Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9942" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9942</a><br>A sandbox information disclosure exists in Twig before 1.38.0 and 2.x before 2.7.0 because, under some circumstances, it is possible to call the __toString() method on an object even if not allowed by the security policy in place.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9947" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9947</a><br>An issue was discovered in urllib2 in Python 2.x through 2.7.16 and urllib in Python 3.x through 3.7.2. CRLF injection is possible if the attacker controls a url parameter, as demonstrated by the first argument to urllib.request.urlopen with \r\n (specifically in the query string or PATH_INFO) followed by an HTTP header or a Redis command. This is similar to CVE-2019-9740.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9948" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9948</a><br>urllib in Python 2.x through 2.7.16 supports the local_file: scheme, which makes it easier for remote attackers to bypass protection mechanisms that blacklist file: URIs, as demonstrated by triggering a urllib.urlopen(‘local_file:///etc/passwd’) call.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9956" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9956</a><br>In ImageMagick 7.0.8-35 Q16, there is a stack-based buffer overflow in the function PopHexPixel of coders/ps.c, which allows an attacker to cause a denial of service or code execution via a crafted image file.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9960" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9960</a><br>The downloadZip function in application/controllers/admin/export.php in LimeSurvey through 3.16.1+190225 allows a relative path.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9970" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9970</a><br>Open Whisper Signal (aka Signal-Desktop) through 1.23.1 and the Signal Private Messenger application through 4.35.3 for Android are vulnerable to an IDN homograph attack when displaying messages containing URLs. This occurs because the application produces a clickable link even if (for example) Latin and Cyrillic characters exist in the same domain name, and the available font has an identical representation of characters from different alphabets.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2016-10743" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2016-10743</a><br>hostapd before 2.6 does not prevent use of the low-quality PRNG that is reached by an os_random() function call.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9942&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9942&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sandbox info
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.22</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-22/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-22/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.806Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.801Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9924" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9924</a><br>rbash in Bash before 4.4-beta2 did not prevent the shell user from modifying BASH_CMDS, thus allowing the user to execute any command with the permissions of the shell.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1716" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1716</a><br>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Software for Cisco IP Phone 7800 Series and Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition or execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability exists because the software improperly validates user-supplied input during user authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device using HTTP and supplying malicious user credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a DoS condition, or to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the app user. Cisco fixed this vulnerability in the following SIP Software releases: 10.3(1)SR5 and later for Cisco Unified IP Conference Phone 8831; 11.0(4)SR3 and later for Cisco Wireless IP Phone 8821 and 8821-EX; and 12.5(1)SR1 and later for the rest of the Cisco IP Phone 7800 Series and 8800 Series.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1763" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1763</a><br>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Software for Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization, access critical services, and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the software fails to sanitize URLs before it handles requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to critical services and cause a DoS condition. This vulnerability affects Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series products running a SIP Software release prior to 11.0(5) for Wireless IP Phone 8821 and 8821-EX; and 12.5(1)SR1 for the IP Conference Phone 8832 and the rest of the IP Phone 8800 Series. Cisco IP Conference Phone 8831 is not affected.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1764" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1764</a><br>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Software for Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on a targeted device via a web browser and with the privileges of the user. This vulnerability affects Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series products running a SIP Software release prior to 11.0(5) for Wireless IP Phone 8821 and 8821-EX; and 12.5(1)SR1 for the IP Conference Phone 8832 and the rest of the IP Phone 8800 Series. Cisco IP Conference Phone 8831 is not affected.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1765" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1765</a><br>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Software for Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to write arbitrary files to the filesystem. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation and file-level permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading invalid files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write files in arbitrary locations on the filesystem. This vulnerability affects Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series products running a SIP Software release prior to 11.0(5) for Wireless IP Phone 8821 and 8821-EX; and 12.5(1)SR1 for the IP Conference Phone 8832 and the rest of the IP Phone 8800 Series.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1766" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1766</a><br>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Software for Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high disk utilization, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the affected software does not restrict the maximum size of certain files that can be written to disk. An attacker who has valid administrator credentials for an affected system could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, remote connection request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write a file that consumes most of the available disk space on the system, causing application functions to operate abnormally and leading to a DoS condition. This vulnerability affects Cisco IP Phone 8800 Series products running a SIP Software release prior to 12.5(1)SR1.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9924&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9924&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;rbash in Bash 
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.21</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-21/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-21/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.804Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.801Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9857" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9857</a><br>In the Linux kernel through 5.0.2, the function inotify_update_existing_watch() in fs/notify/inotify/inotify_user.c neglects to call fsnotify_put_mark() with IN_MASK_CREATE after fsnotify_find_mark(), which will cause a memory leak (aka refcount leak). Finally, this will cause a denial of service.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9894" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9894</a><br>A remotely triggerable memory overwrite in RSA key exchange in PuTTY before 0.71 can occur before host key verification.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9895" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9895</a><br>In PuTTY versions before 0.71 on Unix, a remotely triggerable buffer overflow exists in any kind of server-to-client forwarding.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9896" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9896</a><br>In PuTTY versions before 0.71 on Windows, local attackers could hijack the application by putting a malicious help file in the same directory as the executable.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9897" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9897</a><br>Multiple denial-of-service attacks that can be triggered by writing to the terminal exist in PuTTY versions before 0.71.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9898" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9898</a><br>Potential recycling of random numbers used in cryptography exists within PuTTY before 0.71.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9903" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9903</a><br>PDFDoc::markObject in PDFDoc.cc in Poppler 0.74.0 mishandles dict marking, leading to stack consumption in the function Dict::find() located at Dict.cc, which can (for example) be triggered by passing a crafted pdf file to the pdfunite binary.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6690" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6690</a><br>python-gnupg 0.4.3 allows context-dependent attackers to trick gnupg to decrypt other ciphertext than intended. To perform the attack, the passphrase to gnupg must be controlled by the adversary and the ciphertext should be trusted. Related to a “CWE-20: Improper Input Validation” issue affecting the affect functionality component.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6714" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6714</a><br>An issue was discovered in BlogEngine.NET through 3.3.6.0. A path traversal and Local File Inclusion vulnerability in PostList.ascx.cs can cause unauthenticated users to load a PostView.ascx component from a potentially untrusted location on the local filesystem. This is especially dangerous if an authenticated user uploads a PostView.ascx file using the file manager utility, which is currently allowed. This results in remote code execution for an authenticated user.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6716" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6716</a><br>An unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Wicket Core in LogonBox Nervepoint Access Manager 2013 through 2017 allows a remote attacker to enumerate internal Active Directory usernames and group names, and alter back-end server jobs (backup and synchronization jobs), which could allow for the possibility of a Denial of Service attack via a modified jobId parameter in a runJob.html GET request.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6778" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6778</a><br>In QEMU 3.0.0, tcp_emu in slirp/tcp_subr.c has a heap-based buffer overflow.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6973" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6973</a><br>Sricam IP CCTV cameras are vulnerable to denial of service via multiple incomplete HTTP requests because the web server (based on gSOAP 2.8.x) is configured for an iterative queueing approach (aka non-threaded operation) with a timeout of several seconds.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7161" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7161</a><br>An issue was discovered in Zoho ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus 5.x through build 5704. It uses fixed ciphering keys to protect information, giving the capacity for an attacker to decipher any protected data.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7221" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7221</a><br>The KVM implementation in the Linux kernel through 4.20.5 has a Use-after-Free.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7222" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7222</a><br>The KVM implementation in the Linux kernel through 4.20.5 has an Information Leak.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7383" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7383</a><br>An issue was discovered on Systrome Cumilon ISG-600C, ISG-600H, and ISG-800W devices with firmware V1.1-R2.1_TRUNK-20181105.bin. A shell command injection occurs by editing the description of an ISP file. The file network/isp/isp_update_edit.php does not properly validate user input, which leads to shell command injection via the des parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7384" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7384</a><br>An authenticated shell command injection issue has been discovered in Raisecom ISCOM HT803G-U, HT803G-W, HT803G-1GE, and HT803G GPON products with the firmware version ISCOMHT803G-U_2.0.0_140521_R4.1.47.002 or below. The value of the fmgpon_loid parameter is used in a system call inside the boa binary. Because there is no user input validation, this leads to authenticated code execution on the device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7385" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7385</a><br>An authenticated shell command injection issue has been discovered in Raisecom ISCOM HT803G-U, HT803G-W, HT803G-1GE, and HT803G GPON products with the firmware version ISCOMHT803G-U_2.0.0_140521_R4.1.47.002 or below, The values of the newpass and confpass parameters in /bin/WebMGR are used in a system call in the firmware. Because there is no user input validation, this leads to authenticated code execution on the device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7386" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7386</a><br>A Denial of Service issue has been discovered in the Gecko component of KaiOS 2.5 10.05 (platform 48.0.a2) on Nokia 8810 4G devices. When a crafted web page is visited with the internal browser, the Gecko process crashes with a segfault. Successful exploitation could lead to the remote code execution on the device.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7391" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7391</a><br>ZyXEL VMG3312-B10B DSL-491HNU-B1B v2 devices allow login/login-page.cgi CSRF.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7432" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7432</a><br>PHP Scripts Mall Rental Bike Script 2.0.3 has HTML injection via the STREET field in the Profile Edit section.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7438" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7438</a><br>cgi-bin/qcmap_web_cgi on JioFi 4G M2S 1.0.2 devices has XSS and HTML injection via the mask POST parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7440" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7440</a><br>JioFi 4G M2S 1.0.2 devices have CSRF via the SSID name and Security Key field under Edit Wi-Fi Settings (aka a SetWiFi_Setting request to cgi-bin/qcmap_web_cgi).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7441" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7441</a><br>cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_cart in the WooCommerce PayPal Checkout Payment Gateway plugin 1.6.8 for WordPress allows Parameter Tampering in an amount parameter (such as amount_1), as demonstrated by purchasing an item for lower than the intended price.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-8997" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-8997</a><br>An XML External Entity Injection (XXE) vulnerability in the Management System (console) of BlackBerry AtHoc versions earlier than 7.6 HF-567 could allow an attacker to potentially read arbitrary local files from the application server or make requests on the network by entering maliciously crafted XML in an existing field.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3855" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3855</a><br>An integer overflow flaw which could lead to an out of bounds write was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way packets are read from the server. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to execute code on the client system when a user connects to the server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3858" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3858</a><br>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 when a specially crafted SFTP packet is received from the server. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3859" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3859</a><br>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the _libssh2_packet_require and _libssh2_packet_requirev functions. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3862" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3862</a><br>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SSH_MSG_CHANNEL_REQUEST packets with an exit status message and no payload are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3871" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3871</a><br>A vulnerability was found in PowerDNS Authoritative Server before 4.0.7 and before 4.1.7. An insufficient validation of data coming from the user when building a HTTP request from a DNS query in the HTTP Connector of the Remote backend, allowing a remote user to cause a denial of service by making the server connect to an invalid endpoint, or possibly information disclosure by making the server connect to an internal endpoint and somehow extracting meaningful information about the response<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5490" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5490</a><br>Certain versions between 2.x to 5.x (refer to advisory) of the NetApp Service Processor firmware were shipped with a default account enabled that could allow unauthorized arbitrary command execution. Any platform listed in the advisory Impact section may be affected and should be upgraded to a fixed version of Service Processor firmware IMMEDIATELY.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6116" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6116</a><br>In Artifex Ghostscript through 9.26, ephemeral or transient procedures can allow access to system operators, leading to remote code execution.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6279" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6279</a><br>ChinaMobile PLC Wireless Router GPN2.4P21-C-CN devices with firmware W2001EN-00 have an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability via the cgi-bin/webproc?getpage=html/index.html subpage=wlsecurity URI, allowing an Attacker to change the Wireless Security Password.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6282" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6282</a><br>ChinaMobile PLC Wireless Router GPN2.4P21-C-CN devices with firmware W2001EN-00 have CSRF via the cgi-bin/webproc?getpage=html/index.html subpage=wlsecurity URI, allowing an Attacker to change the Wireless Security Password.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6441" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6441</a><br>An issue was discovered on Shenzhen Coship RT3050 4.0.0.40, RT3052 4.0.0.48, RT7620 10.0.0.49, WM3300 5.0.0.54, and WM3300 5.0.0.55 devices. The password reset functionality of the router doesn’t have backend validation for the current password and doesn’t require any type of authentication. By making a POST request to the apply.cgi file of the router, the attacker can change the admin username and password of the router.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6454" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6454</a><br>An issue was discovered in sd-bus in systemd 239. bus_process_object() in libsystemd/sd-bus/bus-objects.c allocates a variable-length stack buffer for temporarily storing the object path of incoming D-Bus messages. An unprivileged local user can exploit this by sending a specially crafted message to PID1, causing the stack pointer to jump over the stack guard pages into an unmapped memory region and trigger a denial of service (systemd PID1 crash and kernel panic).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6492" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6492</a><br>SmartDefragDriver.sys (2.0) in IObit Smart Defrag 6 never frees an executable kernel pool that is allocated with user defined bytes and size when IOCTL 0x9C401CC4 is called. This kernel pointer can be leaked if the kernel pool becomes a “big” pool.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-6501" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-6501</a><br>In QEMU 3.1, scsi_handle_inquiry_reply in hw/scsi/scsi-generic.c allows out-of-bounds write and read operations.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-20555" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-20555</a><br>The Design Chemical Social Network Tabs plugin 1.7.1 for WordPress allows remote attackers to discover Twitter access_token, access_token_secret, consumer_key, and consumer_secret values by reading the dcwp_twitter.php source code. This leads to Twitter account takeover.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-20669" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-20669</a><br>An issue where a provided address with access_ok() is not checked was discovered in i915_gem_execbuffer2_ioctl in drivers/gpu/drm/i915/i915_gem_execbuffer.c in the Linux kernel through 4.19.13. A local attacker can craft a malicious IOCTL function call to overwrite arbitrary kernel memory, resulting in a Denial of Service or privilege escalation.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0191" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0191</a><br>Apache Karaf kar deployer reads .kar archives and extracts the paths from the “repository/“ and “resources/“ entries in the zip file. It then writes out the content of these paths to the Karaf repo and resources directories. However, it doesn’t do any validation on the paths in the zip file. This means that a malicious user could craft a .kar file with “..” directory names and break out of the directories to write arbitrary content to the filesystem. This is the “Zip-slip” vulnerability - <a href="https://snyk.io/research/zip-slip-vulnerability" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://snyk.io/research/zip-slip-vulnerability</a>. This vulnerability is low if the Karaf process user has limited permission on the filesystem. Any Apache Karaf releases prior 4.2.3 is impacted.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-13798" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-13798</a><br>A vulnerability has been identified in SICAM A8000 CP-8000 (All versions &lt; V14), SICAM A8000 CP-802X (All versions &lt; V14), SICAM A8000 CP-8050 (All versions &lt; V2.00). Specially crafted network packets sent to port 80/TCP or 443/TCP could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service condition of the web server. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems on port 80/TCP or 443/TCP. Successful exploitation requires no system privileges and no user interaction. An attacker could use the vulnerability to compromise availability of the web server. A system reboot is required to recover the web service of the device. At the time of advisory update, exploit code for this security vulnerability is public.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-14745" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-14745</a><br>Buffer overflow in prot_get_ring_space in the bcmdhd4358 Wi-Fi driver on the Samsung Galaxy S6 SM-G920F G920FXXU5EQH7 allows an attacker (who has obtained code execution on the Wi-Fi chip) to overwrite kernel memory due to improper validation of the ring buffer read pointer. The Samsung ID is SVE-2018-12029.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-15498" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-15498</a><br>YSoft SafeQ Server 6 allows a replay attack.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-16563" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-16563</a><br>A vulnerability has been identified in Firmware variant IEC 61850 for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions &lt; V4.35), Firmware variant MODBUS TCP for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant DNP3 TCP for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant IEC104 for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant Profinet IO for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), SIPROTEC 5 relays with CPU variants CP300 and CP100 and the respective Ethernet communication modules (All versions &lt; V7.82), SIPROTEC 5 relays with CPU variants CP200 and the respective Ethernet communication modules (All versions &lt; V7.58). Specially crafted packets to port 102/tcp could cause a denial-of-service condition in the affected products. A manual restart is required to recover the EN100 module functionality of the affected devices. Successful exploitation requires an attacker with network access to send multiple packets to the affected products or modules. As a precondition the IEC 61850-MMS communication needs to be activated on the affected products or modules. No user interaction or privileges are required to exploit the vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow causing a Denial-of-Service condition of the network functionality of the device, compromising the availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18435" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18435</a><br>KioWare Server 4.9.6 allows local users to gain privileges by replacing \kioware_com\KWSS.exe with a Trojan horse program, because \kioware_com has “Everyone: (F)” permissions.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18473" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18473</a><br>A hidden backdoor on PATLITE NBM-D88N, NHL-3FB1, and NHL-3FV1N devices allows attackers to enable an SSH daemon via the “kankichi” or “kamiyo4” password to the _secret1.htm URI. Subsequently, the default password of root for the root account allows an attacker to conduct remote code execution and as a result take over the system.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18798" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18798</a><br>Attendance Monitoring System 1.0 has SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter to student/index.php?view=view, event/index.php?view=view, and user/index.php?view=view.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18862" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18862</a><br>BMC Remedy Mid-Tier 7.1.00 and 9.1.02.003 for BMC Remedy AR System has Incorrect Access Control in ITAM forms, as demonstrated by TLS%3APLR-Configuration+Details/Default+Admin+View/, AST%3AARServerConnection/Default+Admin+View/, and AR+System+Administration%3A+Server+Information/Default+Admin+View/.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18881" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18881</a><br>A Denial of Service (DOS) issue was discovered in ControlByWeb X-320M-I Web-Enabled Instrumentation-Grade Data Acquisition module 1.05 with firmware revision v1.05. An authenticated user can configure invalid network settings, stopping TCP based communications to the device. A physical factory reset is required to restore the device to an operational state.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18882" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18882</a><br>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) issue was discovered in ControlByWeb X-320M-I Web-Enabled Instrumentation-Grade Data Acquisition module 1.05 with firmware revision v1.05. An authenticated user can inject arbitrary script via setup.html in the web interface.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19487" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19487</a><br>The WP-jobhunt plugin before version 2.4 for WordPress does not control AJAX requests sent to the cs_employer_ajax_profile() function through the admin-ajax.php file, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to enumerate information about users.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19488" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19488</a><br>The WP-jobhunt plugin before version 2.4 for WordPress does not control AJAX requests sent to the cs_reset_pass() function through the admin-ajax.php file, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to reset the password of a user’s account.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19524" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19524</a><br>An issue was discovered on Shenzhen Skyworth DT741 Converged Intelligent Terminal (G/EPON+IPTV) SDOTBGN1, DT721-cb SDOTBGN1, and DT741-cb SDOTBGN1 devices. A long password to the Web_passwd function allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (segmentation fault) or achieve unauthenticated remote code execution because of control of registers S0 through S4 and T4 through T7.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19525" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19525</a><br>An issue was discovered on Systrome ISG-600C, ISG-600H, and ISG-800W 1.1-R2.1_TRUNK-20180914.bin devices. There is CSRF via /ui/?g=obj_keywords_add and /ui/?g=obj_keywords_addsave with resultant XSS because of a lack of csrf token validation.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19872" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19872</a><br>An issue was discovered in Qt 5.11. A malformed PPM image causes a division by zero and a crash in qppmhandler.cpp.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-19985" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-19985</a><br>The function hso_get_config_data in drivers/net/usb/hso.c in the Linux kernel through 4.19.8 reads if_num from the USB device (as a u8) and uses it to index a small array, resulting in an object out-of-bounds (OOB) read that potentially allows arbitrary read in the kernel address space.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-16255" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-16255</a><br>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler Insteon Hub 2245-222 - Firmware version 1012. Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can send an authenticated HTTP request at At 0x9d014e84 the value for the cmd1 key is copied using strcpy to the buffer at $sp+0x280. This buffer is 16 bytes large.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-1992" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-1992</a><br>The IBM Power 9 OP910, OP920, and FW910 boot firmware’s bootloader is responsible for loading and validating the initial boot firmware image that drives the rest of the system’s hardware initialization. The bootloader firmware contains a buffer overflow vulnerability such that, if an attacker were able to replace the initial boot firmware image with a very carefully crafted and sufficiently large, malicious replacement, it could cause the bootloader, during the load of that image, to overwrite its own instruction memory and circumvent secure boot protections, install trojans, etc. IBM X-Force ID: 154345.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-3963" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-3963</a><br>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the DHCP daemon configuration of the CUJO Smart Firewall. When adding a new static DHCP address, its corresponding hostname is inserted into the dhcpd.conf file without prior sanitization, allowing for arbitrary execution of system commands. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker can send a DHCP request message and set up the corresponding static DHCP entry.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-3968" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-3968</a><br>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the verified boot protection of the Das U-Boot from version 2013.07-rc1 to 2014.07-rc2. The affected versions lack proper FIT signature enforcement, which allows an attacker to bypass U-Boot’s verified boot and execute an unsigned kernel, embedded in a legacy image format. To trigger this vulnerability, a local attacker needs to be able to supply the image to boot.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-3969" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-3969</a><br>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the verified boot protection of the CUJO Smart Firewall. It is possible to add arbitrary shell commands into the dhcpd.conf file, that persist across reboots and firmware updates, and thus allow for executing unverified commands. To trigger this vulnerability, a local attacker needs to be able to write into /config/dhcpd.conf.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-3985" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-3985</a><br>An exploitable double free vulnerability exists in the mdnscap binary of the CUJO Smart Firewall. When parsing mDNS packets, a memory space is freed twice if an invalid query name is encountered, leading to arbitrary code execution in the context of the mdnscap process. An unauthenticated attacker can send an mDNS message to trigger this vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-4003" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-4003</a><br>An exploitable heap overflow vulnerability exists in the mdnscap binary of the CUJO Smart Firewall running firmware 7003. The string lengths are handled incorrectly when parsing character strings in mDNS resource records, leading to arbitrary code execution in the context of the mdnscap process. An unauthenticated attacker can send an mDNS message to trigger this vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-4011" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-4011</a><br>An exploitable integer underflow vulnerability exists in the mdnscap binary of the CUJO Smart Firewall, version 7003. When parsing SRV records in an mDNS packet, the “RDLENGTH” value is handled incorrectly, leading to an out-of-bounds access that crashes the mdnscap process. An unauthenticated attacker can send an mDNS message to trigger this vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-4030" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-4030</a><br>An exploitable vulnerability exists the safe browsing function of the CUJO Smart Firewall, version 7003. The bug lies in the way the safe browsing function parses HTTP requests. The “Host” header is incorrectly extracted from captured HTTP requests, which would allow an attacker to visit any malicious websites and bypass the firewall. An attacker could send an HTTP request to exploit this vulnerability.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-6461" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-6461</a><br>Remote file inclusion allows an attacker to craft a specific URL referencing the Schneider Electric Modicon BMXNOC0401, BMXNOE0100, BMXNOE0110, BMXNOE0110H, BMXNOR0200H, BMXP342020, BMXP342020H, BMXP342030, BMXP3420302, BMXP3420302H, or BMXP342030H PLC web server, which, when launched, will result in the browser redirecting to a remote file via a Java script loaded with the web page.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2015-6462" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2015-6462</a><br>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (nonpersistent) allows an attacker to craft a specific URL, which contains Java script that will be executed on the Schneider Electric Modicon BMXNOC0401, BMXNOE0100, BMXNOE0110, BMXNOE0110H, BMXNOR0200H, BMXP342020, BMXP342020H, BMXP342030, BMXP3420302, BMXP3420302H, or BMXP342030H PLC client browser.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2016-5819" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2016-5819</a><br>Moxa G3100V2 Series, editions prior to Version 2.8, and OnCell G3111/G3151/G3211/G3251 Series, editions prior to Version 1.7 allows a reflected cross-site scripting attack which may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the user?s browser within the trust relationship between their browser and the server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-16231" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-16231</a><br><strong> DISPUTED </strong> In PCRE 8.41, after compiling, a pcretest load test PoC produces a crash overflow in the function match() in pcre_exec.c because of a self-recursive call. NOTE: third parties dispute the relevance of this report, noting that there are options that can be used to limit the amount of stack that is used.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-16232" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-16232</a><br><strong> DISPUTED </strong> LibTIFF 4.0.8 has multiple memory leak vulnerabilities, which allow attackers to cause a denial of service (memory consumption), as demonstrated by tif_open.c, tif_lzw.c, and tif_aux.c. NOTE: Third parties were unable to reproduce the issue.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-16253" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-16253</a><br>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler Insteon Hub 2245-222 - Firmware version 1012 for the cc channel of Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can send an authenticated HTTP request At 0x9d014dd8 the value for the id key is copied using strcpy to the buffer at $sp+0x290. This buffer is 32 bytes large, sending anything longer will cause a buffer overflow.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-16254" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-16254</a><br>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler Insteon Hub 2245-222 - Firmware version 1012. Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can send an authenticated HTTP request at 0x9d014e4c the value for the flg key is copied using strcpy to the buffer at $sp+0x270. This buffer is 16 bytes large, sending anything longer will cause a buffer overflow.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9857&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9857&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Linux k
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.14</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-14/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-14/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.802Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.801Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9768" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9768</a><br>Thinkst Canarytokens through commit hash 4e89ee0 (2019-03-01) relies on limited variation in size, metadata, and timestamp, which makes it easier for attackers to estimate whether a Word document contains a token.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9787" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9787</a><br>WordPress before 5.1.1 does not properly filter comment content, leading to Remote Code Execution by unauthenticated users in a default configuration. This occurs because CSRF protection is mishandled, and because Search Engine Optimization of A elements is performed incorrectly, leading to XSS. The XSS results in administrative access, which allows arbitrary changes to .php files. This is related to wp-admin/includes/ajax-actions.php and wp-includes/comment.php.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3816" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3816</a><br>Openwsman, versions up to and including 2.6.9, are vulnerable to arbitrary file disclosure because the working directory of openwsmand daemon was set to root directory. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted HTTP request to openwsman server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3833" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3833</a><br>Openwsman, versions up to and including 2.6.9, are vulnerable to infinite loop in process_connection() when parsing specially crafted HTTP requests. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious HTTP request to cause denial of service to openwsman server.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12220" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12220</a><br>Logic bug in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables a privileged user to execute arbitrary code via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12221" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12221</a><br>Insufficient input validation in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause an integer overflow via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12222" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12222</a><br>Insufficient input validation in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause an out of bound memory read via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12223" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12223</a><br>Insufficient access control in User Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to escape from a virtual machine guest-to-host via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12224" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12224</a><br>Buffer leakage in igdkm64.sys in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18089" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18089</a><br>Multiple out of bounds read in igdkm64.sys in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18090" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18090</a><br>Out of bounds read in igdkm64.sys in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18091" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18091</a><br>Use after free in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 may allow an unprivileged user to potentially enable a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12191" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12191</a><br>Bounds check in Kernel subsystem in Intel CSME before version 11.8.60, 11.11.60, 11.22.60 or 12.0.20, or Intel(R) Server Platform Services before versions 4.00.04.383 or SPS 4.01.02.174, or Intel(R) TXE before versions 3.1.60 or 4.0.10 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially execute arbitrary code via physical access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12192" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12192</a><br>Logic bug in Kernel subsystem in Intel CSME before version 11.8.60, 11.11.60, 11.22.60 or 12.0.20, or Intel(R) Server Platform Services before version SPS_E5_04.00.04.393.0 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially bypass MEBx authentication via physical access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12198" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12198</a><br>Insufficient input validation in Intel(R) Server Platform Services HECI subsystem before version SPS_E5_04.00.04.393.0 may allow privileged user to potentially cause a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12201" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12201</a><br>Buffer overflow vulnerability in Platform Sample / Silicon Reference firmware for 8th Generation Intel(R) Core Processor, 7th Generation Intel(R) Core Processor, Intel(R) Pentium(R) Silver J5005 Processor, Intel(R) Pentium(R) Silver N5000 Processor, Intel(R) Celeron(R) J4105 Processor, Intel(R) Celeron(R) J4005 Processor, Intel Celeron(R) N4100 Processor and Intel(R) Celeron N4000 Processor may allow privileged user to potentially execute arbitrary code via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12202" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12202</a><br>Privilege escalation vulnerability in Platform Sample/ Silicon Reference firmware for 8th Generation Intel(R) Core Processor, 7th Generation Intel(R) Core Processor may allow privileged user to potentially leverage existing features via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12203" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12203</a><br>Denial of service vulnerability in Platform Sample/ Silicon Reference firmware for 8th Generation Intel Core Processor, 7th Generation Intel Core Processor may allow privileged user to potentially execute arbitrary code via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12204" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12204</a><br>Privilege escalation vulnerability in Platform Sample/ Silicon Reference firmware Intel(R) Server Board, Intel(R) Server System and Intel(R) Compute Module may allow privileged user to potentially execute arbitrary code via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12205" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12205</a><br>Privilege escalation vulnerability in Platform Sample/ Silicon Reference firmware for 8th Generation Intel(R) Core Processor, 7th Generation Intel(R) Core Processor may allow unauthenticated user to potentially execute arbitrary code via physical access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12208" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12208</a><br>Buffer overflow in HECI subsystem in Intel(R) CSME before versions 11.8.60, 11.11.60, 11.22.60 or 12.0.20 and Intel(R) TXE version before 3.1.60 or 4.0.10, or Intel(R) Server Platform Services before version 5.00.04.012 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially execute arbitrary code via physical access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12209" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12209</a><br>Insufficient access control in User Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to read device configuration information via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12210" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12210</a><br>Multiple pointer dereferences in User Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12211" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12211</a><br>Insufficient input validation in User Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12212" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12212</a><br>Buffer overflow in User Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12213" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12213</a><br>Potential memory corruption in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12214" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12214</a><br>Potential memory corruption in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables a privileged user to execute arbitrary code via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12215" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12215</a><br>Insufficient input validation in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables a privileged user to cause a denial of service via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12216" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12216</a><br>Insufficient input validation in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables a privileged user to execute arbitrary code via local access via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12217" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12217</a><br>Insufficient access control in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows<em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables a privileged user to read device configuration information via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12218" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12218</a><br>Unhandled exception in User Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows</em> before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to cause a memory leak via local access.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-12219" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-12219</a><br>Insufficient input validation in Kernel Mode Driver in Intel(R) Graphics Driver for Windows* before versions 10.18.x.5059 (aka 15.33.x.5059), 10.18.x.5057 (aka 15.36.x.5057), 20.19.x.5063 (aka 15.40.x.5063) 21.20.x.5064 (aka 15.45.x.5064) and 24.20.100.6373 potentially enables an unprivileged user to read memory via local access via local access.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9768&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9768&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinkst Canary
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.13</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-13/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-13/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.800Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.797Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9741" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9741</a><br>An issue was discovered in net/http in Go 1.11.5. CRLF injection is possible if the attacker controls a url parameter, as demonstrated by the second argument to http.NewRequest with \r\n followed by an HTTP header or a Redis command.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1723" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1723</a><br>A vulnerability in the Cisco Common Services Platform Collector (CSPC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access an affected device by using an account that has a default, static password. This account does not have administrator privileges. The vulnerability exists because the affected software has a user account with a default, static password. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by remotely connecting to the affected system using this account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to log in to the CSPC using the default account. For Cisco CSPC 2.7.x, Cisco fixed this vulnerability in Release 2.7.4.6. For Cisco CSPC 2.8.x, Cisco fixed this vulnerability in Release 2.8.1.2.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3785" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3785</a><br>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller, versions prior to 1.78.0, contain an endpoint with improper authorization. A remote authenticated malicious user with read permissions can request package information and receive a signed bit-service url that grants the user write permissions to the bit-service.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-17937" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-17937</a><br>gpsd versions 2.90 to 3.17 and microjson versions 1.0 to 1.3, an open source project, allow a stack-based buffer overflow, which may allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on embedded platforms via traffic on Port 2947/TCP or crafted JSON inputs.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9741&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9741&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;An issue was d
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.12</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-12/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-12/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.798Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.797Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9644" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9644</a><br>An XSSI (cross-site inclusion) vulnerability in Jupyter Notebook before 5.7.6 allows inclusion of resources on malicious pages when visited by users who are authenticated with a Jupyter server. Access to the content of resources has been demonstrated with Internet Explorer through capturing of error messages, though not reproduced with other browsers. This occurs because Internet Explorer’s error messages can include the content of any invalid JavaScript that was encountered.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9644&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;An XSSI (cross
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.11</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-11/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-11/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.796Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.793Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9687" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9687</a><br>PoDoFo 0.9.6 has a heap-based buffer overflow in PdfString::ConvertUTF16toUTF8 in base/PdfString.cpp.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9692" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9692</a><br>class.showtime2_image.php in CMS Made Simple (CMSMS) before 2.2.10 does not ensure that a watermark file has a standard image file extension (GIF, JPG, JPEG, or PNG).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9705" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9705</a><br>Vixie Cron before the 3.0pl1-133 Debian package allows local users to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via a large crontab file because an unlimited number of lines is accepted.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9706" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9706</a><br>Vixie Cron before the 3.0pl1-133 Debian package allows local users to cause a denial of service (use-after-free and daemon crash) because of a force_rescan_user error.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-1890" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-1890</a><br>IBM SDK, Java Technology Edition Version 8 on the AIX platform uses absolute RPATHs which may facilitate code injection and privilege elevation by local users. IBM X-Force ID: 152081.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9687&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9687&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;PoDoFo 0.9.6 h
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.08</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-08/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-08/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.794Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.793Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9631" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9631</a><br>Poppler 0.74.0 has a heap-based buffer over-read in the CairoRescaleBox.cc downsample_row_box_filter function.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9634" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9634</a><br>Go through 1.12 on Windows misuses certain LoadLibrary functionality, leading to DLL injection.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9636" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9636</a><br>Python 2.7.x through 2.7.16 and 3.x through 3.7.2 is affected by: Improper Handling of Unicode Encoding (with an incorrect netloc) during NFKC normalization. The impact is: Information disclosure (credentials, cookies, etc. that are cached against a given hostname). The components are: urllib.parse.urlsplit, urllib.parse.urlparse. The attack vector is: A specially crafted URL could be incorrectly parsed to locate cookies or authentication data and send that information to a different host than when parsed correctly.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9637" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9637</a><br>An issue was discovered in PHP before 7.1.27, 7.2.x before 7.2.16, and 7.3.x before 7.3.3. Due to the way rename() across filesystems is implemented, it is possible that file being renamed is briefly available with wrong permissions while the rename is ongoing, thus enabling unauthorized users to access the data.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9638" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9638</a><br>An issue was discovered in the EXIF component in PHP before 7.1.27, 7.2.x before 7.2.16, and 7.3.x before 7.3.3. There is an uninitialized read in exif_process_IFD_in_MAKERNOTE because of mishandling the maker_note-&gt;offset relationship to value_len.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9639" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9639</a><br>An issue was discovered in the EXIF component in PHP before 7.1.27, 7.2.x before 7.2.16, and 7.3.x before 7.3.3. There is an uninitialized read in exif_process_IFD_in_MAKERNOTE because of mishandling the data_len variable.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9640" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9640</a><br>An issue was discovered in the EXIF component in PHP before 7.1.27, 7.2.x before 7.2.16, and 7.3.x before 7.3.3. There is an Invalid Read in exif_process_SOFn.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9641" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9641</a><br>An issue was discovered in the EXIF component in PHP before 7.1.27, 7.2.x before 7.2.16, and 7.3.x before 7.3.3. There is an uninitialized read in exif_process_IFD_in_TIFF.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2017-3164" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2017-3164</a><br>Server Side Request Forgery in Apache Solr, versions 1.3 until 7.6 (inclusive). Since the “shards” parameter does not have a corresponding whitelist mechanism, a remote attacker with access to the server could make Solr perform an HTTP GET request to any reachable URL.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9631&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9631&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poppler 0.74.0
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.07</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-07/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-07/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.792Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.793Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9624" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9624</a><br>Webmin 1.900 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by leveraging the “Java file manager” and “Upload and Download” privileges to upload a crafted .cgi file via the /updown/upload.cgi URI.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-7175" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-7175</a><br>In ImageMagick before 7.0.8-25, some memory leaks exist in DecodeImage in coders/pcd.c.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-5019" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-5019</a><br>A heap-based overflow vulnerability exists in the PowerPoint document conversion function of Rainbow PDF Office Server Document Converter V7.0 Pro R1 (7,0,2018,1113). While parsing Document Summary Property Set stream, the getSummaryInformation function is incorrectly checking the correlation between size and the number of properties in PropertySet packets, causing an out-of-bounds write that leads to heap corruption and consequent code execution.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0192" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-0192</a><br>In Apache Solr versions 5.0.0 to 5.5.5 and 6.0.0 to 6.6.5, the Config API allows to configure the JMX server via an HTTP POST request. By pointing it to a malicious RMI server, an attacker could take advantage of Solr’s unsafe deserialization to trigger remote code execution on the Solr side.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-14498" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-14498</a><br>get_8bit_row in rdbmp.c in libjpeg-turbo through 1.5.90 and MozJPEG through 3.3.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (heap-based buffer over-read and application crash) via a crafted 8-bit BMP in which one or more of the color indices is out of range for the number of palette entries.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-18815" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2018-18815</a><br>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated users to bypass authorization checks for portions of the HTTP interface to the JasperReports Server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.’s TIBCO JasperReports Server: 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9624&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9624&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Webmin 1.900 a
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.06</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-06/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-06/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.790Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.789Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9591" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9591</a><br>A reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ShoreTel Connect ONSITE before 19.49.1500.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the brandUrl parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9592" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9592</a><br>A reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ShoreTel Connect ONSITE 19.45.1602.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the url parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9593" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9593</a><br>A reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ShoreTel Connect ONSITE 18.82.2000.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the page parameter.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-3824" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-3824</a><br>A flaw was found in the way an LDAP search expression could crash the shared LDAP server process of a samba AD DC in samba before version 4.10. An authenticated user, having read permissions on the LDAP server, could use this flaw to cause denial of service.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1543" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1543</a><br>ChaCha20-Poly1305 is an AEAD cipher, and requires a unique nonce input for every encryption operation. RFC 7539 specifies that the nonce value (IV) should be 96 bits (12 bytes). OpenSSL allows a variable nonce length and front pads the nonce with 0 bytes if it is less than 12 bytes. However it also incorrectly allows a nonce to be set of up to 16 bytes. In this case only the last 12 bytes are significant and any additional leading bytes are ignored. It is a requirement of using this cipher that nonce values are unique. Messages encrypted using a reused nonce value are susceptible to serious confidentiality and integrity attacks. If an application changes the default nonce length to be longer than 12 bytes and then makes a change to the leading bytes of the nonce expecting the new value to be a new unique nonce then such an application could inadvertently encrypt messages with a reused nonce. Additionally the ignored bytes in a long nonce are not covered by the integrity guarantee of this cipher. Any application that relies on the integrity of these ignored leading bytes of a long nonce may be further affected. Any OpenSSL internal use of this cipher, including in SSL/TLS, is safe because no such use sets such a long nonce value. However user applications that use this cipher directly and set a non-default nonce length to be longer than 12 bytes may be vulnerable. OpenSSL versions 1.1.1 and 1.1.0 are affected by this issue. Due to the limited scope of affected deployments this has been assessed as low severity and therefore we are not creating new releases at this time. Fixed in OpenSSL 1.1.1c-dev (Affected 1.1.1-1.1.1b). Fixed in OpenSSL 1.1.0k-dev (Affected 1.1.0-1.1.0j).</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9591&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9591&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reflected Cr
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.03.05</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-05/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-03-05/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:09:33.788Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:09:33.785Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9213" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9213</a><br>In the Linux kernel before 4.20.14, expand_downwards in mm/mmap.c lacks a check for the mmap minimum address, which makes it easier for attackers to exploit kernel NULL pointer dereferences on non-SMAP platforms. This is related to a capability check for the wrong task.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9578" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9578</a><br>In devs.c in Yubico libu2f-host before 1.1.8, the response to init is misparsed, leaking uninitialized stack memory back to the device.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9213&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-9213&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Linux k
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>2019.02.27</title>
    <link href="http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-02-27/"/>
    <id>http://cve.justshuoz.com/2019/04/10/2019-02-27/</id>
    <published>2019-04-10T13:06:06.395Z</published>
    <updated>2019-04-10T13:06:06.389Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1559" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-1559</a><br>If an application encounters a fatal protocol error and then calls SSL_shutdown() twice (once to send a close_notify, and once to receive one) then OpenSSL can respond differently to the calling application if a 0 byte record is received with invalid padding compared to if a 0 byte record is received with an invalid MAC. If the application then behaves differently based on that in a way that is detectable to the remote peer, then this amounts to a padding oracle that could be used to decrypt data. In order for this to be exploitable “non-stitched” ciphersuites must be in use. Stitched ciphersuites are optimised implementations of certain commonly used ciphersuites. Also the application must call SSL_shutdown() twice even if a protocol error has occurred (applications should not do this but some do anyway). Fixed in OpenSSL 1.0.2r (Affected 1.0.2-1.0.2q).<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9208" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9208</a><br>In Wireshark 2.4.0 to 2.4.12 and 2.6.0 to 2.6.6, the TCAP dissector could crash. This was addressed in epan/dissectors/asn1/tcap/tcap.cnf by avoiding NULL pointer dereferences.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9209" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9209</a><br>In Wireshark 2.4.0 to 2.4.12 and 2.6.0 to 2.6.6, the ASN.1 BER and related dissectors could crash. This was addressed in epan/dissectors/packet-ber.c by preventing a buffer overflow associated with excessive digits in time values.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9210" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9210</a><br>In AdvanceCOMP 2.1, png_compress in pngex.cc in advpng has an integer overflow upon encountering an invalid PNG size, which results in an attempted memcpy to write into a buffer that is too small. (There is also a heap-based buffer over-read.)<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9211" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9211</a><br>There is a reachable assertion abort in the function write_long_string_missing_values() in data/sys-file-writer.c in libdata.a in GNU PSPP 1.2.0 that will lead to denial of service.<br><a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-9214" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CVE-2019-9214</a><br>In Wireshark 2.4.0 to 2.4.12 and 2.6.0 to 2.6.6, the RPCAP dissector could crash. This was addressed in epan/dissectors/packet-rpcap.c by avoiding an attempted dereference of a NULL conversation.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1559&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-1559&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;If an applicat
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
